Register of the Karl H. Von Wiegand papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- PHOTOGRAPHS, 1911-circa 1960 (Boxes 82-83, Photo file)
  - 306 prints, miscellaneous travel shots, undated (Envelope II-KK)
  - 19 travel post cards, undated (Envelope LL)
  - 5 original drawings by Langley, undated (Envelope MM)
  - 19 prints relating to aviation, undated (Envelope NN)
  - 7 oversize prints relating to China, undated (Envelope mOO)
  - 4 miscellaneous oversize prints, undated (Envelope mPP)
  - 16 prints depicting the Graf Zeppelin's round-the-world voyage, 1929 (Envelope QQ)
- MEMORABILIA, undated (Memorabilia 85)
  One Middle Eastern sword, one Ethiopian sword, and one Ethiopian shield. Use copies of items available in Box 85.